[{"answer": "I'm sorry", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Not bad", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I've been praying for him since I heard", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Oh, Lord", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "No, I promise...  not a chance. I own this guy. There was no one else. I'm on the move too much. Trust me", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yes. Your dog is fine, my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I'm filling in. We don't know if she's coming back. She might have to get a job closer to home", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What the heck do you mean", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I am trying to keep emotions out of this. Even though this is an important issue to me and I have strong feelings about the subject", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yes, I do, as a matter of fact... and to prove it I have not gotten personal and you have. Why aren't you at work? You're not sick", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yes, you write more than anyone else. Yes, you make us a lot of money, but isn't there someone more appropriate to..", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " my friend, I'll try", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What's it mean", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh God, this is like a nightmare", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Emergency room only", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Once the tests come back, is there someone I can reach in your office for the results", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "His home number", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You waiting for me to say something?  What sort of thing do you want? Look, I'll be at the restaurant tomorrow", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What needs clearing up", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Come on in", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I'm not sure", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Then I guess we do", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " Two crab dinners and pitcher of cold beer.  Baked or fries", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " One baked", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I don't want to hear that music right now", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I don't", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Here are the keys to my apartment. I'm going to park you in my place while I take my friend home", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I'll take you... why not", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "What job", "docId": "As-Good-As-It-Gets.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "What are you doing here", "qsentId": 32}]